Guide to the AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council Records, 1902-2004; 0450-019; 7.43 cubic feet (8 boxes and 1 tube)
  - DIRECTORIES, 1927-1995; SERIES III (Box-folder 4/1-4/15; 7/4)
    - Directories, 1927-1995; Subseries A (Box-folder 4/1-4/12; 4/15; 7/4)
      - Washington State Labor Council, 1957-1995; Part 2 (Box-folder 4/2-4/10)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 4/2)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1962-1963, 1965, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 4/3)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1966-1967, 1969-1970, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 4/4)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1971, 1973 (Box-folder 4/5)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1980, 1981 (Box-folder 4/6)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 4/7)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1987 (Box-folder 4/8)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1988 (Box-folder 4/9)
        - Washington State Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1995 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - King County Labor Council, 1959; Part 3 (Box-folder 4/11)
        - King County Labor Council Directory of Organizations, 1959 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Washington State Legislature, 1957-1963; Part 4 (Box-folder 4/12)
        - Washington State Legislature Directory, 1957, 1963 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Associated General Contractors of America, 1957-1958; Part 5 (Box-folder 4/15)
        - Associated General Contractors of America Roster of Membership, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Correspondence About Directories, 1965-1983; Subseries B (Box-folder 4/13-4/14)
      - Washington State Labor Council Directory Printing and Distribution Correspondences, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Washington State Labor Council Directory General Information Correspondences, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 4/14)
  - CONSTITUTIONS, 1947-1988; SERIES IV (Box-folder 4/16-4/20)
    - Washington State Federation of Labor Constitution, 1947 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Oregon State Labor Council Constitution and Merger Agreement, 1956 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - King County Labor Council Constitution, 1959 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Washington State Building and Construction Trades Council Constitution, 1960 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Washington State Labor Council Constitution, 1972, 1974, 1988, 1972-1988 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - LOCAL CHAPTER DOCUMENTS, 1957-1960; SERIES V (Box-folder 4/21-4/24)
    - Columbia Power Trades Council, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Columbia Basin Trades Council, 1960 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 1957 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Waitresses Union Local No. 240, 1960 (Box-folder 4/24)
  - HISTORIES, 1924-1986; SERIES VI (Box-folder 4/33-4/38)
    - History of the Washington State Federation of Labor, 1924 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - History of the Washington State Federation of Labor, 1954 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - Duplicate History of the Washington State Federation of Labor, 1954 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - One Hundred Years of American Labor, 1981 (Box-folder 4/36)
    - Labor History, 1986 (Box-folder 4/37)
    - The Everett Massacre: 70 Years Later, 1986 (Box-folder 4/38)
  - TRUSTS AND PENSIONS, 1970-1986; SERIES VII (Box-folder 4/39-4/42; 5/1-5/2)
    - Labor Trust Services, Inc., 1970-1986; Subseries A (Box-folder 4/39-4/42)
      - Labor Trust Services, Inc.: Articles of Incorporation and Bylaws, 1970 (Box-folder 4/39)
      - Labor Trust Services, Inc.: Minutes, 1970-1986 (Box-folder 4/40)
      - Labor Trust Services, Inc,: Stock Certificates, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 4/41)
      - Labor Trust Services, Inc.: Stock Transfer Ledger, 1971 (Box-folder 4/42)
    - Welfare and Pension Administration Services, Inc., 1971-1986; Subseries B (Box-folder 5/1-5/2)
      - Welfare and Pension Administration Service, Inc.: Corporate Minutes, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 5/1-2)
  - MISSION TO POLAND, 1995; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 4/43-4/44)
    - Mission to Poland, 1995 (Box-folder 4/43)
    - Mission to Poland: Ephemera, 1995 (Box-folder 4/44)
  - BAY VISTA BUILDING, INC., 1985; SERIES IX (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Bay Vista Building, Inc. Bylaws and Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - NEWSPAPERS, 1953-1965; SERIES X (Box-folder 7/3)
    - WSLC Newspapers and Clippings, 1953-1965 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - BANNER, SERIES XI (Box-folder Box 8)
    - Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO: Fighting for Working Families, Undated (Box-folder 8)
  - PHOTOGRAPHIC SLIDES, 1982; SERIES XII (Box-folder 9/1-9/2)
    - Marvin Williams and Larry Kenny Roast, 1982; Subseries A (Box-folder 9/1)
      - 412 Roast Slides: Marvin Williams and Larry Kenny in Various Poses, 1982; 34 slides (Box-folder 9/1)
    - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Subseries B (Box-folder 9/2)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Slides, Undated; 40 slides (Box-folder 9/2)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS, 1976-1979; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 9/3-9/5)
    - Pictures for Committee on Political Education Tabloid, 1976 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Convention Proceedings 1979 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Photographs, Undated (Box-folder 9/5)